<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="faq_1_question">What exactly is an <b>email alias?</b></string>
    <string name="faq_1_answer">Email alias is similar to forward email address: all emails sent to an alias will be forwarded to your inbox.\n\nThanks to SimpleLogin technology, you can also send emails <b>from</b> an alias.\n\nFor your contact, the alias is therefore your email address.</string>
    <string name="faq_2_question">Why do I need SimpleLogin</string>
    <string name="faq_2_answer">When you give away your personal email online, there is a good chance that your email address would end up with a spammer or leaked during a breach. You could check whether your email is leaked using website like have i been pwned?.\n\nSimpleLogin could also help manage <u>your business emails</u>. If you own a domain and don\'t want to pay a full solution like GSuite, you could add the domain into SimpleLogin and create emails like <b>contact@my-domain.com</b>, <b>partner@my-domain.com</b> with aliases. All our business emails (the <b>@simplelogin.io</b>) are actually aliases.</string>
    <string name="faq_3_question">What is the difference between SimpleLogin and other email forwarding services?</string>
    <string name="faq_3_answer">• Fully open source: both SimpleLogin server and client code (browser extension, JS library) are open source so anyone can freely inspect and (hopefully) improve the code. You wouldn\'t trust a blackbox to handle your emails, would you?\n\n• No ads, no tracker.\n\n• The only email forwarding solution that is <u>self-hostable</u>, i.e. you could run SimpleLogin on your server. With our detailed self-hosting instructions and most of components running as Docker container, anyone who knows ssh is able to deploy SimpleLogin on their server.\n\n• You can send/reply emails from alias. There\'s also no caps or limits on this feature.\n\n• Not just email alias: SimpleLogin is also a privacy-focused and developer-friendly identity provider that:\n  - respects user privacy\n  - is simple to use for developers.\nSimpleLogin is a privacy-focused alternative to the \"Login with Facebook/Google/Apple\" buttons.\n\n• Plenty of features: browser extension, custom domain, catch-all alias, OAuth libraries, etc. and much more to come.\n\n• Open roadmap at Trello: you know the exciting features we are working on.</string>
    <string name="faq_4_question">Do you read the forwarded emails?</string>
    <string name="faq_4_answer">Technically the emails DO go through SimpleLogin server but email content is NEVER read. SimpleLogin is open source so anyone could freely inspect the code on Github.</string>
    <string name="faq_5_question">Do you store the forwarded emails?</string>
    <string name="faq_5_answer">No, SimpleLogin never stores any forwarded email. You can see how emails are handled in our code on Github. Also simply forwarding emails is much easier and cheaper than storing, indexing,… your emails.</string>
    <string name="faq_6_question">What happens if SimpleLogin is gone?</string>
    <string name="faq_6_answer">This is probably the hardest question that a company has to answer :).\n\nAs we are using SimpleLogin on a daily basis, for both our personal and professinal usage, in the worst case, we will close registrations for new users so SimpleLogin can only be used by existing users.\n\nFor information, Spamgourmet, a similar email forwarding service has been running for more than 20 years now. Spamgourmet is actually an inspiration for SimpleLogin.\n\nIf all this is still not enough, you can also run a SimpleLogin instance yourself as SimpleLogin code is open source and we give detailed instructions on how to run it</string>
    <string name="faq_7_question">How SimpleLogin is different than temporary email services?</string>
    <string name="faq_7_answer">SimpleLogin alias are permanent as opposed to the temporary emails created on services like temp-mail.org, 10minutemail.net, etc.\nSimpleLogin also doesn\'t store the emails.\nWe are simply different products for different usecases.</string>
    <string name="faq_8_question">What is <b>alias directory</b> or <b>catch-all</b> features?</string>
    <string name="faq_8_answer">These 2 features both allow you to create alias <u>on-the-fly</u>, meaning you don\'t have to open SimpleLogin to create a new alias.\n\nEnabling <b>catch-all</b> on your domain allows you to use <u>ANYTHING@my-domain.com</u> as alias with <b>ANYTHING</b> being any word. The only limit is it has to have less than 128 characters.\n\n<b>Alias Directory</b> is similar to catch-all, you can use <u>your_directory+ANYTHING@simplelogin.co</u> as alias. <b>your_directory</b> is the name of the directory you created.</string>
    <string name="faq_9_question">I receive an email forwarded to my personal email from an alias. How can I reply to that email? Do I need to go to SimpleLogin to initiate the reply?</string>
    <string name="faq_9_answer">You can reply directly from your email client. Just click on the \"reply\" button, the reply will be routed via SimpleLogin and SimpleLogin will make it coming from your alias. Your personal email will stay invisible to the original sender.\n\nTechnically, the <b>From</b> header in your email is replaced by a special alias dynamically generated for each sender. When you reply, your reply is actually sent to this special alias and SimpleLogin will relay the reply back to the sender, making sure the email is sent from your alias. All information about your personal email address is removed during that process.</string>
    <string name="faq_10_question">Are my emails modified?</string>
    <string name="faq_10_answer">No your email content is forwarded <b>as-is</b>, attachments included. SimpleLogin doesn\'t modify email content and only relies on email <b>headers</b> to do its \"magic\".</string>
    <string name="faq_11_question">What is a <b>reverse-alias</b>?</string>
    <string name="faq_11_answer">A reverse-alias is a <b>special</b> alias that allows you to send email <b>from your alias</b>.\n\nA reverse-alias is created for each alias you want to send email from and each contact you want to send email to.\n\nWhen you send an email to a reverse-alias from your personal email, the email will be sent from your alias to the contact.</string>
    <string name="faq_12_question">Is email alias permanent?</string>
    <string name="faq_12_answer">As a normal email address, an email alias is always there unless you delete it.</string>
    <string name="faq_13_question">Where is SimpleLogin server located?</string>
    <string name="faq_13_answer">We use UpCloud, a Finland cloud provider. Our server is currently located in its France-Germany datacenter.</string>
    <string name="faq_14_question">I don\'t find answer to my question here</string>
    <string name="faq_14_answer">Please send your question to <b>hi@simplelogin.io</b>. You can also create an issue on our GitHub Issues.</string>
</resources>